{
    "subject": "resource/Clay_Davidson",
    "predicate": "ontology/instrument",
    "object": "resource/Guitar",
    "human_readable": "The instrument played by Clay Davidson is Guitar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9311896562576294,
            "question": "What instrument does Clay Davidson play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8804770708084106,
            "question": "Is Clay Davidson a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8040123581886292,
            "question": "What kind of music might Clay Davidson play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.79319828748703,
            "question": "Are there any famous guitar players that Clay Davidson admires?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7494215965270996,
            "question": "Does Clay Davidson use any other instruments besides the guitar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6987472772598267,
            "question": "Has Clay Davidson ever performed publicly with his guitar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5235275626182556,
            "question": "What is the name of Clay Davidson's band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5154577493667603,
            "question": "Has Clay Davidson ever taken guitar lessons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.239736869931221,
            "question": "Does Clay Davidson write his own songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14238636195659637,
            "question": "What genres of music are often associated with the guitar?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The instrument played by Clay Davidson is Guitar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8282_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Clay Davidson write his own songs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8282_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Clay Davidson ever taken guitar lessons?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8282_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Clay Davidson's band?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8282_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8282_60.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Talents : Vocals, Guitar\" for Clay Davidson, which supports the statement that he plays the guitar."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}